(Leonard:)All right, we gave it 45 minutes.
(Leonard:)It's no longer funny.
Let's try something else.
(Sheldon:)What do you propose?
Uh... On three, both of you
bounce the balls as hard as you can.
(Leonard:)Highest bounce wins the office.
(Kripke:)Oh, you are going down, Cooper.
l don't think so, Kripke.
l've bounced many a rubber ball
in my day.
(Leonard:)All right. That's enough trash talk.
(Leonard:)One, two, three.
(Howard:)Sheldon was higher.
(Leonard:)Congratulations, Sheldon,
you win the office.
(Sheldon:)Who's unsatisfactory in PE now?
MAN & WOMAN
We go together
Like rama lama lama
Ke ding a de dinga a dong
(Amy:)Oh, what a great movie.
l cannot believe
you've never seen Grease.
(Amy:)My mother didn't allow me
to watch it.
(Amy:)She was afraid it might encourage me
to join a gang.
l gotta go. I gotta get up early.
(Bernadette:)My company's testing a new steroid
that doesn't shrink testicles...